david thanks for taking time away from
waiting for sandler to write grown-ups
three to be here pete's dad never got to
see him on snl because he passed away on
9 11.
pete's mom has never seen him on snl
because she blinks
[Applause]
i want to thank spade for hosting
tonight he was he is amazing love you
love you
oh by the way um
snl has just released a compilation of
david's funniest sketches it's called
the best of chris farley
we're here to honor one of the biggest
stars of 1987
with some of the biggest stars of 1984.
ralph macchio's here
[Music]
ralph's a great guy i drove over here
with him gave him five stars
at one time rob was one of the biggest
stars in the world he was an a-list
actor he was named one of the 50 most
beautiful people in the world and he the
other 49.
these are compliments
is this guy hot or what there's not a
dry in the place
of a cleanup on every chick's chair
for years rob lowe had a sex addiction
but he cured it by getting less famous
rob was in a movie called the outsiders
back in the day
remember that
his character was called sodapop because
at the time rob was 98 coke
i remember the first time i became aware
of rob i was at a casting meeting for
tommy boy when i came across your
headshot and i do mean came across
he's good-looking
it's not easy being rob
he said being so handsome made it
difficult for him to find meaningful
roles
i wanted to ask brad pitt about that but
he was too busy acting in meaningful
roles
[Applause]
rob has a line of skin care products you
can buy them online
you won't but you can
[Laughter]
our younger audience might not know who
you are so kids this is who your mom
thinks about when she's your dad
[Applause]
rob was great on the west wing you
remember that show
i assume your pal charlie sheen helped
you with that he's used to working with
aids
white house aides
what did you get oh
rob looks great for his age many people
have wondered if he's had any plastic
surgery those same people have wondered
if caitlyn jenner has any plastic
surgery
rob came up at a time when a sex tape
could really ruin your career but rob
had to do it the hard way with his
acting
rob was in austin powers too he was
excited to meet the cat mr biglesworth
since it had been a while since he'd
made a movie with a hairless
whoa
macaulay culkin looks worse than i
thought
david thanks for taking time away from
waiting for sandler to write grown-ups
three to be here
david spade's assistant once tried to
kill him in his sleep and the world was
shocked to find out you could afford an
assistant
it's not bad pete davidson pete's dad
never got to see him on snl because he
passed away on 9 11.
pete's mom has never seen him on snl
because she blinks
is pete white is he black and coulter
needs to know so she can decide if she
hates him
pete i actually thought you were black
but i guess you just have your dad's
ashy skin give it up for david spade
tonight as our host doing a great job
thanks david for giving me a copy of
your autobiography before the show david
always keeps a copy on him uh because it
helps him reach the steering wheel
honestly tiny little baby man is what
i'm saying
you may not know this but rob riggle was
a pilot in the marines who got shot down
at snl abc and hbo
[Applause]
things were so tough for him at snl his
call time was sunday morning
it is nice to see my friend david spade
um
you guys are well aware his assistant uh
once tried to murder him which
i don't know i guess the stress of
answering the phone twice a month
finally got to him um
that'd be hard it'd be hard
david spade amazingly um has slept with
some of the most beautiful actresses in
hollywood proving just how ugly show
business makes women feel
[Applause]
she was born in alaska and for the last
20 years her career has been on ice
she will grew up in a house with no
plumbing so she turned her into
music
[Applause]
she'll be leaving right after the show
but her tooth is gonna hang out david
spade our host this evening doing a
fabulous job
you look like a female ellen degeneres
[Applause]
david is perhaps best known for his work
with comedy legend chris farley
tragically chris farley died when his
heart stopped due to a lethal
combination of heroin cocaine and the
stress of carrying david spade through
two movies
if you don't know who jimmy carr is he's
a comic who sells out theaters in
england hong kong thailand and australia
there's a name for that in america
opening act
he looks like his dick wears a monocle
thank you david uh for your first roast
this has got to be really exciting for
you
uh your performance so far reminds me of
my rookie year in the nfl when i threw a
league high 28 interceptions and had
absolutely no clue what i was doing
as we all know i followed in my father's
footsteps but david you forged a path on
your own i know you wanted to follow in
your dad's footsteps but he
snuck out of the house so carefully he
didn't leave any tracks
he's bringing it
but you did it anyway david you went out
and got a business degree from arizona
state
although to be fair i think we all know
that a business degree from arizona
state is just a bar towel that says you
read good
speaking of reading i recently read
spaye's memoir almost interesting
actually i'm lying
you really think the first book i pick
up in 20 years gonna be by the guy who
played dickie roberts former child star
i don't think so
no peyton by the way david that title
almost interesting talk about false
advertising
now if you wanted to be honest you
should have called it almost tall enough
to ride a roller coaster
i'll take it
david spade is dumb and short
sorry
bad
peyton manning is here physically
now come on we love peyton manning we're
lucky to have him tonight i'll never
forget peyton's career
sadly he will
he may be the only person up here who's
been given more head than rob lowe
david spade the host with the most step
stools in your apartment
david you've seriously influenced so
many female comics haircuts
some people say nikki glazer is only
here because she's good looking nothing
could be further from the truth
if you haven't seen nikki's show yet
you're me
i know it's pretty shameless but i'm
gonna stage with a guy who made two
joe dirt films so how shameless can i be
uh
as a right-wing hate monger it's
fantastic to be at a big hollywood
shindig with all these glittering
celebrities that isn't a fundraiser for
obama
i'm hoping to persuade you all to vote
for trump uh but most of all i want you
david um
because it would prove the media is
lying when they say they're that trump
won't get the vote of a single spade
david is the
the perfect roast master for the show
he's successful enough that everyone
knows who he is but not so successful
that he's makes us feel threatened he's
like the mike pence of comedy
a lot of people don't realize that
david's sister is famous designer kate
spade judging by your outfit david i
gather you're not speaking
anne hopes the republicans can hold on
to the house so she can continue to
haunt it
she seems stiff and conservative but
anne gets wild in the sheets just ask
the clan
looks like she's having a good time i
haven't seen you laugh this hard since
trayvon martin got shot
[Applause]
[Music]